Lall, Betty, Files /4080
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Betty Lall Files
1972-1986
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Lall, Betty
/4080
5 cubic feet
5 linear ft.
Records (documents).
3085773
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 13, 2016
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 01, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3012: Alice Cook Papers /4115: ILR School Extension Division Additional Records /4188: Al Nash Additional Files 5619/004: ACTWU President Jacob Sheinkman Files 5736: Barbara Wertheimer Additional Files 5917 P: Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Additional Photographs 6047: Archives Information File
Lall, Betty G. (Betty Goetz); New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Metropolitan District Office. Extension Division.
3085773
- Urban Affairs; International Affairs and Unions; Employment Conference; Training Sessions for UPA District Representatives; Economic Health of City and Region; Gimbels; Afro-American History and American Problems; CLC Alcoholism; Iron Workers; ILGWU L. 23 (Box 1)
  - Urban Affairs - Publications of AFL-CIO, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Urban Affairs, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - International Affairs & Unions DC37 SP '83 Coc. New Rochelle, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Employment Conference, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Training Sessions for UPA District Representatives (2-6-69), 1969 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Economic Health of City and Region (7GM4) - I-2-68, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Gimbels Joint Labor Management Career Development - 1-7-69, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Afro-American History and American Problems (9GM66) - 5-4-70, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - CLC Alcoholism Course, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Iron Workers - 455, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ILGWU - Local 23-25, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - AFSCME - D.C. 37, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - United Automobile Workers Local 259, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Cap Makers - Local 2, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Amal. Cloth. Workers. Jt. Bd. L. R. G., 1975 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Amal. Cloth. Workers. N.Y. Jt. Bd. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Amal. Cloth. W. U. 169, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Congress, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Political Action - Unions, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Follow-up Meetings: Hotel, Hospital, Nursing HomeLocal 144: June 7, '72, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Annual Report, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - India, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - BGL Speeches, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Follow-Up Meeting: International Association of Bridge, Structural Local 455-- July 24- 1972 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - LAC - 3/14/73, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Union Survey, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Office of Non-Collegiate Sponsored Institutions, 1967-1977 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - City Charter Review Conf. Oct. 17, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Community Services Study, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Drug Abuse (Dust. 65), 1969 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Action Nov. 10-11 '76, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Housing; Allied Industrial Workers; Criteria for Union Participation on CHP Boards; Health Education Project, Grant and Correspondence; Correspondence HLAC mailings; Union-University Vocations Project Employment Youths; Economic Dislocation correspondenc (Box 2)
  - Housing, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Allied Ind. Workers, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - OBJ#2: Follow-up: Criteria for Union Participation on CHP Boards (9/28/73), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Health Education Project, Grant and Correspondence, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Corres-HLAC Mailings-Additional Jan. '73- June '75 Copies, 1973-1975 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Union-Univ. Vocational. Proj. Employment Youth, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Econ. Dis: Correspondence, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Retail w/ Dept. Store Workers 1-5 Macy's, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Ed Conf. Foundations, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - United Storeworkers, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - United Federation of Teachers - Local 2, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - IBT 237, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - OBJ#5 Interview No. 20 Int. Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 1205 768-0225, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - OBJ#5 Interview No. 21 Int. Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 810, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - OBJ#5 Interview No. 13 Building Service Employees Local 32E 665-2100 (Bronx), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - OBJ#5 Interview No. 14 Building Service Employees Local 325 685-4700 (N.Y.C.) (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - OBJ#5 Interview No. 15 Bartenders Union 686-3515 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - OBJ#5 Interview No. 16 Carpenters Union, Local 255-0431, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - OBJ#5 Interview No. 17 Retail Clerks Int. Assoc. Local 1111 279-7042 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - OBJ#5 Interview No. 18 Hotel Trades, Local 6 586-1550 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Obj.#3 - Union People as Resource People, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Federal Budget F.Y. 1986 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - ITU - Local 6 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Victims of Crime Workshop, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - OBJ#3 - Field Trip No. 1 2/6/74 Sewage Treatment Plant, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - OBJ#3 - Field Trip #3 - May 8 '74 Maimonides Mental Health Clinic, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Trade Union, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Central Labor Council Urban Affairs, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Urban Affairs Betty Hall and Bienstock, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Action; Follow Up Meeting, Airlines and other unions; Federal Government Project; Correspondence HLAC mailings; Solidarity Seminars; Political Action and Urban Problems; Training Sessions for UFT District Representatives; Parent Grievance Procedures; Heal (Box 3)
  - Trade Union Health Education Project, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Bound
  - Action, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Follow-Up Meeting: Airlines July 27, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Summaries received (11/19/73) (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - NYSSILR, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Fed. Govt. + Project Conference Speaker Corres. 1965 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Memorandums, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Solidarity Seminars, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Political Action and Urban Problems Fall 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Effective Speaking, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Training Sessions for Uft District Representatives (8Gm2I) - 9-27-69, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Parent Grievance Procedure Alternative Proposals - Discussion Outline (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Health Prog., 1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Health Cont., 1974 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - I. Administrative E. Health Union Interviews, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Company Correspondence. Re Conf. May, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Comments on Water, Trans. U.D., Rept., 1966 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Urban Issues Related to Industry and Union (Box 3, Folder 18)
- High School Students Reports of Follow-up Meetings; Youth Employment; Urban Courses; Leadership Training for Union and Community Service; Amalgamated Clothing Workers; International Longshoremen 1814; Shoe Workers; Meat cutters, L. 174 & 342; Communic (Box 4)
  - Reports of Follow-Up Meetings with Unions, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Youth Employ. '72 etc. Proj., 1972 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Leadership Training for Union and Community Service for Manhattan-Bronx Postal Union, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Amal. Clothing Workers National (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - D'Voren Dec. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Shoe Workers, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Amal. Meat cutters Local 174, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Local 342 Amal. Meat cutters, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Int'l. Assoc. of Machinists Dist. 15, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - United Federation of Teachers Local 2, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Communication Workers Local 1109, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - C.W.A. Reg. 3, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Dist. 65, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Employment, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Housing Deter, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - School Dis.t Proj., 1975 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - OBJ#5 Interview No. 3 Int. Brotherhood of Elec. Workers Local 33-30 591-2017, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - OBJ#5 Interview No. 4 Bakery and Conf. Clerks - RCIA Local #150 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Health Care Retirees, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - H. Ed. - Cornell ILR, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Internship Program, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence.-HLAC Mailings - Addition Copies from Feb. 1974:--- (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Future of Union Health Plans 1971 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Union Medical Centers Copies of Interviews, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Expenses RCVD w/o Contracts. A Perlow's hotel Receipt signed hotel voucher., 1974 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Medical Center Study, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Health - Union Health Centers, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Fur Workers, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Furniture's Workers Local 140, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Hospital Workers 1199, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Plumbers - Local 2, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Postal Workers, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Retails Food Clerks Local 1500, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Service Employees 32B, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Brooklyn Naval Yard, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Urban Affairs Course 1, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Urban Affairs Prog. Materials, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Model Cities Course, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Housing Deterioration Inter Prog. Spring '70, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Oatsville - Health Ed. Prog., 1981 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Manpower, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Manpower, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Lall BK Workers + Their Metropolitan Environment (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Housing - Model Cities Conf., 1982 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Solidarity Seminars, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- National Conf. - Program, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Econ. Dis. Conf. Planning, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Econ. Dis. Book - Printer - Promot., 1985 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Book Publication Econ. Dist. + Job Loss, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Econ. Dis. Conf. Corres. Foundations, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Speakers, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Econ. Dev. BK., 1983 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Econ. Dis. Conf. Publication, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Labor Stake Conference: Attendance, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Press Release, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- National Conf. - Projected Budget, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Planning Committee Labor's Stake and Voice in a Changing World Economy, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Labor Stake Conf.: Correspondence - Others, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Labor's Stake and Voice in a Changing World Economy A. Draft Paper on Conference, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Books - Fall 1972 (Box 5, Folder 25)